there are a few things worse than
getting ill
an unexpected cold stomach ache or even
a fever can upset your day
or what if you need help managing a
chronic health condition like diabetes
hypertension or even cancer do you know
where you can get tested or treatment
for many people the answer is no poor
access to information on where to seek
medical care is a big challenge in many
african countries
that's where we at mdoc come in
navihealth.ai is an online directory of
healthcare providers
hospitals clinics diagnostics labs and
pharmacies
throughout africa access information
about the nearest healthcare facility of
your choice such as
opening hours and the services they
provide
get turn-by-turn navigation to access
the services you want
when you need it and be sure to leave
feedback afterwards
to provide support during this trying
period we have expanded the services
available on navihealth.ai
you can now view our kovid19 interactive
map for details and navigation
to over 650 testing centers isolation
sites and treatment centers throughout
africa we also have an online directory
of
african hotline or emergency numbers for
you to call
if you think you or a loved one have
been exposed
and get more guidance on where to get
tested or treated
and we are working to identify the local
manufacturers of ppes
such as face masks hand gloves and
overalls
and other equipment essential to
providing care for those with the
coronavirus infection
these are but a few of the many ways we
continue to evolve to help you better
so why not visit us today at
navihealth.ai
to register your services as a
healthcare provider or facility
share information with us find the
nearest hospital to you
or use one of our platform's many
services
navihealth.ai a directory here for you
and your family